

9597826861

Coimbatore **Q**

00000

00000

00000

https://www.linkedin.com/in/karthika- **in** rajendran-21180a97

SUMMARY

Being a self-motivated content writer with 6+ years of experience in drafting and editing articles for prominent industries, I'm looking to work in a creative environment where my versatile skills can be put to use. As a freelance content writer, I have so far worked on various niches that include Lifestyle, Healthcare, Academics, Industry based blogs etc. I'm specialized in writing blogs, articles, web content, Ads, content for brochures, pamphlets etc. I'm a stringent researcher and believe quality over quantity and assure timely deliverance of projects.

00000

SKILLS

Good Communication Skills, both verbal and written Strategic Thinking

Problem Solving
Creativity

Team Player

EXPERIENCE

Content Writer

vSocialize Pvt Ltd 2015 - 2017

Assigned the tasks of writing original content for different sites like wedding cards, Cuisines and Hotels, property developers etc

Sub Editor

Simplicity 2019 - 2021

Simplicity is an online news portal with hyper local news covering Coimbatore, Tirupur, Mettupalayam and Nilgiris. As a sub editor my job entailed writing news articles based on news drafts given by the reporters.

Content Specialist

Nx Mindworks 2019 - 2022

My role involved developing online and offine promotions for brands matching their brand promise and adhering to their brand qualities. Developing content for brochures, leafet, print ads, online ads, social media, websites, press releases and research reports were part of my output as a Content Specialist

Consultant Content Writer

CG-VAK Software & Exports Ltd 2021 - Present

My role here is to write website SEO content for different clients associated with the company.

EDUCATION

Higher Secondary

Avila Convent Matriculation Higher Secondary School 2009 - 2010

Bsc CT

Sri Krishna College of Engineering and Technology 2010 - 2013

Master of Business Administration

Bharathiar School of Management and Entrepreneurship Development 2013 - 2015

LANGUAGES

English Tamil

Malayalam

• • • • •

0000

Hindi Sindhi

• • • • •